[This program is intended for
audiences aged 13 and over]
[It may contain
explicit visuals, audio, and content;
viewers under the age of 13
should be advised]
[Miss Jarin Tiansawangwarp]
Jane, why is your score this low?
Yeah, why?
Miss,
why is my exam score this low?
What did you get?
I got 18.
The full mark is 30.
It's still more than half.
But I'm sure I got more than that.
It's just all in your head.
Did you mark it wrong?
You've gone too far, Jarin.
How dare you speak to me like that?
Get back to your seat.
No, I won't.
I want to see my answer sheet.
And you have to prove it
in front of the whole classroom
right here.
But if you didn't make any mistakes,
I will bow to you as an apology
in front of the school assembly.
Honestly, I never wanted any trouble,
if she wasn't the best friend
of the health education teacher
that I had beef with.
Excuse me,
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
could I see the one
that has the highest mark?
I got another eight questions right
like they did,
so why weren't mine marked correct?
From that incident,
the whole school knew
about 'Jane Jarin'
as a brave warrior,
reclaiming judgment.
Zon was the first one
from a different classroom
who wanted to be my friend.
The next one was Chawing,
and the reason she wanted
to be my friend
was that she was also treated unfairly
by the same English teacher
after she got into a fight
with her daughter.
Hello.
If you're turning in
your assignment, just put it here.
Miss,
may I say something?
What is it, Miss Jarin?
I really think
you should keep your work
and personal life separate,
or you'll have to be mad at everyone
who fights with your daughter.
But if you really can't
control your temper,
I suggest you make an appointment
with a psychiatrist.
You've gone too far!
Of course, that heroic stunt
I pulled for my friend
sent me right
to the Principal's Office again.
If you want my daughter
to change schools,
you need to prove it fair and square
that this teacher didn't misuse
her position to mistreat a student.
And with how strong Mom was,
everything ended quickly
without me getting punished.
The last one is Nut,
and the reason
she wanted to join the gang was simple.
She just loved my heroism so much
that she looked up to me as her idol.
And that was the beginning
of 'The Goddess Gang,'
with Jane Jarin as the leader!
Come on in.
[Dim Sum]
Is something going on?
I thought you were taking me
to a dessert place.
But buffet is also nice!
I don't have to hold back.
Then let's get inside.
Come on.
When is Darin gonna come?
I'm hungry.
Can we just dig in?
- Just dig in?
- Mm.
- What are we waiting for, then?
- We have something cooked, after all.
What's this? It's sliced pork.
What is this?
- Yo, that one is the good stuff!
- Here she is.
- We're here.
- Hey, Darin, my bestie!
Hi, there.
- Hi, Jane.
- Hello.
- Have a seat, please.
- Thank you.
[Dine 4, Pay for 2, only today!]
Did you ask me out here
just for this sale deal?
Um...
Yes, another one of my friends
couldn't make it.
Right.
And I really thought this was a date.
She literally just tricked me
into being a sharer in this deal.
Goodness me,
I'm crashing out.
Jane, do you realize how cool you were?
Those three teachers that you destroyed
used to horrify the whole school.
Pardon?
I was your senior during high school.
You probably don't remember me,
but all the seniors knew Jane Jarin,
the leader of the Goddess Gang.
Mm, I also knew about this.
Bee told me
that there was this kid
from her high school who was so brave.
I didn't think that was you, Jane.
There's more.
Spill.
Let's shed some light on the teacher
you argued with about your marks.
I accidentally pissed her off once
and got my scores taken away,
but I was too scared to say anything.
I still respect you
just by talking about it again.
The tears are coming.
Are we crying now?
I wasn't brave or anything.
I just wanted to do what's right.
I actually never hated
those teachers or anything.
Whoa, what a speech.
How about a round of applause?
By the way, what do you wanna drink?
Hey,
I'm not giving you a ride
if you get drunk.
I gotta take Jane home.
What?
I'm not drinking.
My bae's gonna pick me up.
Hey!
So you both aren't drinking?
I'm alone in this one?
I'd better not drink, then.
Or maybe
you wanna drink with me, Jane?
I've learned my lesson.
Jane, Imma give this to you.
Right, there you go!
Whoa, here you go.
[Father]
This is yours, Jane.
- There.
- I'm gonna take my father's call, Jane.
Alright.
- Girl, you have hands.
- What?
- Jane.
- Yes?
Actually, Darin wanted to take you
on a date, just the two of you,
but she was too shy!
That's why she dragged us out here.
I didn't want to come here at first,
but she's my friend, right?
So I did what she asked.
I'm just saying
'cause I don't want you to get sad.
It's all fine.
I actually think hanging out
with many people is...pretty fun.
"Pretty fun."
"Pretty fun," my butt!
She took an hour to get here
and changed through ten outfits.
She was afraid you'd find out
she was shy, so she kept it simple.
So much for being chill.
Oh, right.
I have Dai's secret to tell you.
Wanna know?
What is it about?
When she gets shy,
she will cross her arms.
How?
Show her.
Don't forget the face.
Aha, there it is!
Is that a good impression?
If you don't believe me, just observe.
That means...anytime we came across
each other earlier,
and she looked at me
or crossed her arms while we talked,
she was actually blushing!
For real?
What are you chatting about?
Nothing!
No one was gossiping about you!
You're so dramatic.
I'm still chewing.
Yeah.
- Ooh, this is yummy.
- It's not cooked yet.
Oh, is it? Okay.
I didn't notice that.
That's sus.
- Dai?
- Yes?
It's just that...my eyes are burning.
Is it bad?
Come on, I'll take you to the hospital.
They're burning so bad,
probably for...
your unmatched beauty.
Jane!
Where did you get this idea from?
Hm?
Is it Rong?
Not me.
Ouch!
Dai,
my eyes are burning.
- Maybe from the chillis.
- Let me take care of that.
Whoa!
Nope.
Just eat.
Must be nice, right?
Here.
Dai?
Hm?
Have a safe trip back.
It's from Dai.
Why do you have
to be involved with my sister?
Your sister was the one
asking me out,
and I didn't even ask for this dessert.
Tell her no, then!
Nope.
JaneWill!
Ginging!
Don't call me that!
Why not?
You were calling me JaneWill just now.
Do you want a piece of me?
If you slap me, I'll slap you back.
This is my faculty building, too.
Give me the dessert!
Huh!
Wasn't so hard, was it?
Ugh!
Augh!
Don't mock me!
What? Why not?
What's going on, JaneWill?
Who was that?
It's Dai's half-sister,
the Queen of Pharmacy
I told you about.
Should we show her
what our hands can do?
Maybe not.
You're here early today, Waii.
I didn't want my sweet girl
to wait on me.
I can wait,
but just for you, though.
Why are you such a sweet talker?
Are you like this with everyone?
[Pangpond]
Who was that?
Why didn't you pick it up?
They're gonna hang up on their own.
But right now, I'm so hungry!
I am!
You always say that
whenever we meet.
Well, it's true.
School was exhausting.
Why don't you pick up my calls
around this d*mn woman?
Hey, watch your mouth.
Do I have to be nice
to a homewrecker?
That's some bullcrap.
Give me back my girlfriend, woman.
That's a f*cked up thing to say.
We were never official.
Why wouldn't we be?
I know I'm making you blush
whenever we meet eyes.
Just say you're too shy
to admit that you like me.
You're imagining it.
I've never thought of you
as more than a friend.
And if I'm gonna be with someone,
it has to be Waii.
Let's go.
Cake?
What?
I caught her red-handed today.
Caught who?
Your little friend, of course.
She's definitely going after NewYear.
I also found them at a movie theater.
Ah!
That's why Waii has been so sneaky,
just coming in and out.
Can you help me?
Out of all the girls in the world,
why mess with your brother's girl?
Is Waii really a lesbian?
Gosh, Sis!
Isn't that obvious?
You still couldn't figure it out?
What kind of friends are you guys?
What?!
I see why she's never talked
about any guy.
Such a piece of work.
Can you help me handle this?
"Help"?
[Enjoy, from Dai]
Bussin'!
I should draw something for Dai
to repay her for the dessert.
But wait...
what should I draw?
I'll go with this pic.
I'll even change her outfit.
Bingo!
Dai will be an inspiration
for my next comic's female lead.
A story about an enthusiastic architect
who is just starting her career
and loves nightlife,
until, one night, she meets
a sophomore student in college
who goes to a pub because her friends
need her to babysit their table.
But...
would Dai be okay with this?
I need her permission!
Could I have you as a reference
for the female lead in my comic?
Pardon?
Jane...
have you had dinner?
Not yet.
My mom stopped by my dorm
and she brought me
a lot of steamed blue swimmer crab.
Would you like it?
If so, I'll bring you some.
Whoa, a swimmer and crab meat?
I can choose from the two?
It's a steamed blue swimmer crab!
What do you mean?
Is it both a swimmer
and a crab in itself?
I'm telling you right now
that I don't eat swimmers.
I'm downstairs now.
After disappearing for days,
why does she stop by all of a sudden?
[Only students in the university dorm
are allowed entry]
Dai is crossing her arms again.
Wonder what's making her shy.
Steamed blue swimmer crab.
You didn't come see me...
for a week.
Well...
You stole my kiss after all, Jane.
It wasn't a kiss!
It was just a peck!
There's a difference?
There is!
A peck is
just a light touch on the lips,
but a kiss involves tongues!
But it doesn't change the fact
that you stole it from me.
Well...
Then, what do I have to do?
You gotta let me
steal it back, of course,
beautiful.
Not happening!
I'm sorry...
I shouldn't have...
Nuh-uh,
I don't mind it,
but it's just...
I'm definitely gonna explode.
Hm?
Well...
I will explode from shyness!
- Right, Waii?
- What?
I met this boy the other day.
He was such a snack!
Are you free tomorrow?
Can you come with me?
Nah.
Why won't you be?
I know you are.
I'm telling you that I'm not.
Ooh, so you're all
about glamour now, JaneWill?
All of a sudden, you got into makeup.
It's not about glamour.
I bet...
she's in a relationship now.
I'm not!
My lips are just dry!
Dry lips?
You'd only need lipstick for that.
Just let her do whatever she wants to.
As for you,
stop sticking your nose
into others' business.
Whoa, b*tch.
Why are you
turning this around on me?
I'm off. Sick of your face.
What?!
Knock it off!
So basically, you're okay
with Dai now, right?
No way!
What do you mean by "okay"?
No need to hide it from me.
It's written all over your face
already, JaneWill.
But as for Waii...
What about her?
That's gotta be it.
That's for sure.
What's gotta be it?
Waii is definitely a lesbian,
but she's hiding it from us.
[This account is private]
[Requested]
- Oh...
- Ow...
Uh, are you hurt?
I found it just over there.
Thank you!
Here you go.
Milk helps with spice, you know.
Where the hell is Waii?
I bet she's sneaking back home.
Do you think
I have too much makeup on?
Lemme see.
Nuh-uh, I don't think so.
It looks fine.
- It is?
- Mm!
What the hell?!
Give me a sec!
Dai, don't show yourself just yet.
I'm blushing right now.
You're still at it, Jane?
Said the one who got shy for a week!
[Shush it]
What's up with you, JaneWill?
Aw, what's the matter
with you, b*tch?!
Oh, Jane.
How lucky.
Actually, I was coming to find you.
What is it, Champ?
Right...
So...
I have so many photos
of you from the beach,
and I wanted to send them to you,
but you haven't accepted
my follower request.
Uh, I...
You can follow me
since I am JaneWill's bestie.
Right...
Darin!
- Hello.
Hi, there.
Just who I was looking for.
I need your help on a gig.
You're still available, aren't you?
I am.
Then, may I steal Darin
from you for now?
Come on, follow me.
Are you alright, Ging?
He told me
we weren't right for each other.
Is that even a reason?!
More like an excuse to break up.
Uh...
calm down.
You just got into a fight.
He's gonna call you
when he feels better.
It's been two weeks with none of that.
What?
Then, why didn't you text him first?
He blocked me on LINE
and also my number.
Oh...
Jane, drink this with me.
I think I'm good.
What?
Ging.
Ging?
Ding, ding, ding!
What?
If she's this drunk,
then how's she getting home?
Ging, come lie down here.
Go! One, two, go!
Wait, what's happening?
Are you gonna throw up? Wait!
Hold it in!
Hold it!
Here.
Get your head outta there.
Up!
Let's get you back
to where you were.
Jeez...
Will I get any sleep tonight?
Rise and shine.
It's morning already!
I bought you rice porridge.
Hurry up and eat it.
Aren't you eating?
I'm not hungry just yet.
You drew Dai in a cartoon style,
JaneWill?
That's pretty cute.
What?
Why are you taking a photo?
Don't show it to Dai.
I don't want her to see it just yet.
I guarantee I'll zip it.
Enjoy your food.
I'm heading back to my dorm now.
I'll send you off downstairs.
It's fine.
I'm fine on my own.
I love you, bestie!
I...
trust Dai with you.
What in the world?
Junior, come help me with my stuff.
Hey,
aren't you really gonna help?
There's so much of it!
How many days?
What?
How many days
are you gonna last here?
You'll move your stuff back, eventually.
Oh, Jimmy!
What's all this?
Are you guys fighting again?
This time, I won't budge.
I'm done...
This is the end of it.
Hello.
Hello, Mild.
What's happening between you two?
Jimmy, I'm sorry I stayed out late.
Here is your prawn pad Thai.
I already bought it for you.
You left me starving
for two agonizing hours.
Come on, son.
As a man, you need to hang in there.
You can snack on something
if you get hungry.
Here, I'll put it on a plate.
I'm not eating that!
- I'll take it. It looks delicious.
- Hey, give it back!
It's mine!
Mild bought it for me.
You weren't eating it, right?
- Give that to me!
- Nope!
- Give it to me, Junior.
- Heck no.
- Give it to me!
- Give it to me.
- Junior!
I was just playing, Mom.
Mild, stay the night here, darling.
It's already late.
You can go back tomorrow.
Of course.
Uh...
I'll take care of this.
[The drawing is absolutely beautiful]
[The drawing is...]
Yes, Dai?
The drawing you did for me is stunning.
Dai, you already saw it?
Yep, Ging sent it to me.
Do you really like it, Dai?
I love it!
Can I use this as a profile picture?
Jane?
Are you okay?
I'm good.
I'm just blushing!
She doesn't pick up my calls.
Bee, where has Dai disappeared to?
Nothing is happening to her, right?
What?
Bee doesn't even read my texts.
Rong, where has Dai disappeared to?
Nothing is happening to her, right?
Oh, Darin is probably
trying to meet her deadline.
The professor set it for tonight.
She's probably very busy now.
Yeah, I'm also worried
about her myself.
I've seen that when she works hard
on something, she skips meals.
The next thing we know,
we need to take her to the hospital.
What should we do?
I'm worried sick.
You can buy her
noodles from my shop.
Are you trying to meet your sales?
Oh, Jane! Hi!
- Hello, Rong.
- Come on in.
Just a sec.
There! Okay...
Here's my dad.
- Oh, hi, kiddo.
- Hello.
That's my grandma,
and that's my older brother.
And this is Jane,
a freshman from my university.
Have you eaten, dear?
Not yet.
Any recommendations?
Recommendations...
Our signature dish would be
chicken noodles and king crab noodles.
Uh, then...
what does Dai like?
For Dai, it'd be the chicken one.
Her favorite since childhood.
Then, I'll have
two chicken noodles to go
and one king crab noodle to eat here.
Coming right up.
How much, Rong?
- Uh...
- It's alright, dear.
It's on the house.
Excuse me just a sec, Jane.
Dad!!
What?!
- Dad!
- What?
Grandma gave out free food again!
Mom!
Please go get some rest, Mom.
Nueng, take her inside.
Just another sec, Jane.
It's just that my grandma
is pretty oblivious,
thinking customers
are her relatives.
Just last month, she let people
eat for free for almost 2,000 baht.
And it's gonna be 220 baht for you.
The drinks are on me.
- Here you go, Rong.
- Alright, thank you.
Hold on a second.
- Alright.
- Okay.
And does Dai live alone
or with someone at her dorm?
Just alone.
She doesn't like to share her space.
Such a private person, that one.
I think she's moved out
to live alone since high school.
Alright, location sent.
Her place is on the sixth floor.
- Thank you, Rong.
- Sure.
If you need more information,
don't forget to stop by my shop again.
There's so much to spill.
It's definitely this one!
Jane!
How did you get here?
By motorbike taxi!
You're just...
something else.
Sorry, my place is so messy right now.
You can sit here for now.
It's fine.
I'm just bringing you some food.
I was afraid
you'd work so hard that you'd faint.
This is from Rong's shop, right?
How did you know that?
He doesn't care about me.
He just wanted to find his dad
some customers.
Whenever anyone looks for me,
he always tells them
to buy noodles from him.
It's ingenious marketing.
Sounds like...
someone is regularly visiting.
She's slyer than I realized.
Or maybe...
she's hiding someone in her room?
Jane, are you okay?
That means there's always someone
coming to see you, right?
Mm...
Well,
there are some friends.
But no visits matter more than yours.
Do you know how happy I was
seeing you at my doorstep?
I'll put these in the bowls,
so we can eat them together.
Let me tie my hair up first.
Jane!
You're drooling!
I'm not thinking of
anything inappropriate!
I'm leaving!
What about the noodles?!
Jane!
You're drooling!
I'm not thinking of
anything inappropriate!
[Thank you, beautiful]
[Soon, I'll release a sapphic comic
on a new platform]
[Waiting]
[I'm waiting]
[So excited]
[Counting the days]
[Waiting, waiting, and waiting]
[Looking forward to it, Jane]
What now?
- What got you smiling like that?
- Hm?
Well, the post about the GL comic
that I just started writing
was liked and shared
by so many people last night!
This one is going viral for sure!
Ooh!
[Mommy]
Hello?
What did you say?
I'll be there really soon.
Why? What's going on?
I need to go home.
What's the matter with her?
No idea.
Jelly has crossed the rainbow bridge...
My intention
to plant a tree on her grave
is for us to remember that Jelly
will always be with us,
not anywhere else.
Why are we meant to cross paths
only to part ways?
I hate this feeling.
Death...
is an eternal truth,
both for pets
and humans.
Soon enough,
Mom and I
will have to leave you guys behind.
I...
want you guys
to live with strength.
Don't say that, Dad.
Let's get inside
and let Jelly rest in peace.
[Directed by SUEASIAM STUDIO]
Your friend is an a**hole
for turning NewYear into a lesbian!
Your parents raised you well,
just for you
to think about ending it all
because of a girl?!
I don't want to deny who I am,
and I think I'm a lesbian.
Hi, Dad.
Hi, sweetie.
Will you be my girlfriend, Jane?